

Guosheng Lin

My name is Guo-Sheng Lin, currently employed at Marvell with the title of Senior Engineer, Software Validation & Quality Assurance. In my role, I am primarily responsible for the development and deployment of automated testing scripts. I graduated from the Graduate Institute of Biomedical Electronics and Bioinformatics at National Taiwan University, specializing in biomedical spectroscopy. Additionally, I have taken courses related to chip design and processes, such as Computer-aided VLSI System Design, providing me with a solid background in the semiconductor industry.



P Hsinchu, Hsinchu City, Taiwan in 😱





Work Experience



Senior Engineer, Software Validation & Quality Assurance • Marvell Technology

January 2023 - Present

Utilizing qTest for test management, Jenkins for continuous integration, and the pytest framework for automated script development, I implemented a streamlined process. Additionally, I employed a Raspberry Pi as a platform for swift automation script deployment. This approach involves configuring the firmware version for testing on the target machine, resulting in a significant time-saving of over 50% by minimizing manual testing efforts.

Associate Software Quality Assurance Engineer • Marvell Technology

July 2022 - January 2023

I independently completed the Quarch-related test cases, integrating SSD hot-swapping tests into the automated testing framework. Simultaneously, I assisted in the development of modules for the automation testing of HPE Wondermiddel.



Assistant at the Core Laboratory of Graduate Institute of Biomedical Electronics and Bioinformatics · NTU

April 2020 - June 2022

Assistant for the Introduction to Biomedical Engineering course • NTU

September 2021 - February 2022

Assistant in the Electrical Engineering Department. • NTU

September 2020 - June 2021

Education



2020 - 2023

National Taiwan University

Graduate Institute of Biomedical Electronics and Bioinformatics



2016 - 2020

National Chung Hsin University

Life Science

Skills

- Python
- PyTorch
- MATLAB
- Java
- SPSS Statistics

- Pytest
- Jinkins
- Machine Learning
- Verilog

Languages

• English – Intermediate

• Japanese – Beginner

Frontiers in Physics

Non-Invasive Quantification of Layer-Specific Intrinsic Fluorescence From Mucosa of the Uterine Cervix Using Monte-Carlo-Based Models

Full Aritcle

Biomedical Imaging and Sensing Conference

Two-step curve fitting combined with a two-layered tissue model to quantify intrinsicfl uorescence of cervical mucosal tissue in vivo

Full Aritcle